<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://map1eum.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://map1eum.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2024-12-20T12:26:20+00:00</updated><id>https://map1eum.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">CloudyMap1e</title><subtitle>A enthusiast of technology and future. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">2024F Term Is Over!</title><link href="https://map1eum.github.io/blog/2024/name-test/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2024F Term Is Over!"/><published>2024-12-19T17:30:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-12-19T17:30:00+00:00</updated><id>https://map1eum.github.io/blog/2024/name-test</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://map1eum.github.io/blog/2024/name-test/"><![CDATA[<p>Finals are done, and I should be okay. The CPSC 418 onsite final may be a bit bad, but fortunately, I did very well on the take-home final. I expect to get around 90 (I left a 10-point question blank, but I expect to get full marks on all the other questions).</p> <p>For CPSC 421, I got some true/false questions wrong, but I should have solved all the other questions perfectly, except for the 5-point question that asked if PSPACE belongs to EXPTIME. I did answer it correctly, but some of my steps may not have been perfect. Anyway, I expect to get at least 80.</p> <p>The counting problems in CPSC 418 made me frustrated, but I should still be able to get an average grade without too much trouble.</p> <p>FREN 101 makes me a bit sad, but I should be fine. Especially since my recent grades for participation and the project were not bad.</p> <p>I have no doubt about FRST 303; I should get around 80 if there are no issues.</p> <p>So, I only have one term left at UBC in Canada, and then I will return home and finish my last two courses online.</p> <p>I am still thinking about which courses to take next term. CPSC 440, CPSC 436R, and GERN 304 are already on my mind, but I am still deciding on the last one: CPSC 416 or CPSC 420.</p> <p>I also need to think about whether I want to take four or five courses next term. If I take five, I will definitely have another arts course.</p> <p>My current decision is between taking four courses and two online courses or taking five courses and one online course.</p> <p>Recently, I need to pay close attention to the capital market. Today, I lost 1,000 USD because I chose to sleep in and didn’t sell at 7:30 am. In recent days, I may have more trades than usual because I need to avoid huge losses. The Friday market is very dangerous, but I have no choice now. I just checked the overnight market, and it’s a big dip, as expected.</p> <p>I really need to forget about what others, like Buffett, say and develop my own trading strategy, philosophy, and system. I will sell when the risk goes up and immediately buy back when the risk eases up.</p> <p>So far, I haven’t made any serious mistakes, just like in my academic career. That’s good. If I don’t make any serious mistakes, like going to UBC, I will eventually find my way.</p> <p>I’ll relax for a few days and prepare for the next term. Oh, and I have realized that I have no talent for FPS games. So, it’s over; I’ll just watch some pro players’ highlights and do what I need to do.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="general"/><category term="introduction"/><category term="first-post"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is my first post on this blog.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My First Post</title><link href="https://map1eum.github.io/blog/2024/my-first-post/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My First Post"/><published>2024-11-28T11:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-11-28T11:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://map1eum.github.io/blog/2024/my-first-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://map1eum.github.io/blog/2024/my-first-post/"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to my first post on this blog! I’m excited to start sharing my thoughts and experiences with you. Stay tuned for more updates and interesting content.</p> <p>This post is written on Thanksgiving Day, that marked my almost ending of my first half of final academic year life… I decided to move out of that shitty basement and it’s such a good decision that makes me have much more time and energy to focus on my important things.</p> <p>I am working on Microlight project, a system that makes AI have the highest level of intelligence and execute on behalf of humans for many tasks. This project will have a lot of phases considering my current knowledge level and it’s a long way to go. I will first implement most basic functions and resource-related programs first, including the automation ofCAPTCHA, emails, phone, payment verifications and many things like this. I will just do these tedious work little by little.</p> <p>In the meanwhile, I will keep trying my best in investing in the US equity market and other financial instruments. I realized that my career is kind of dead and maybe the investment and quant trading can be my next direction. I will try my best to explore the road for me.</p> <p>I haven’t written posts for a long time. I stopped doing this when I decided to use 24-hour streaming with auto recording by YouTube to replace the daily note and reflection, because I believe soon I will just use AI to generate a summary based on my everyday complete recordings about what I have done. This is truly interesting. (while I am typing this post my stream is still on!)</p> <p>The finals are coming, dates are set. I am not really stressed about this term, because unlike previous academic years I have keep the pace most of the time and will just be fine to get above avg grades, but I may not be able to achieve a excellent grade I anticipated. The dates are:</p> <p><img src="/assets/img/finals.png" width="100%" alt="Finals Dates"/></p> <p>Deep inside I may be disappointed by my current life. I am not sure if I can make it. But whining is truly useless, either kill yourself or make it alive.</p> <p>In the future I may write more posts - dated or topic, with more thinking, some deep insights and some inspirations and so on. Just using streaming video to passively record the life is not good enough, at least in the aspect of improving my productivity.</p> <p>And happy thanksgiving! although my current state of like is really a irony to this holiday. Tonight when I am at X050 lab there is a short guy keeps talking(annoying!) and there is a pretty girl sitting next to him. I haven’t been excited about any girl for a long time, but this girl is really pretty and I can’t help but look at her, and think about my relationship status, like a dessert.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="general"/><category term="introduction"/><category term="first-post"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is my first post on this blog.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Displaying External Posts on Your al-folio Blog</title><link href="https://map1eum.github.io/blog/2022/displaying-external-posts-on-your-al-folio-blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Displaying External Posts on Your al-folio Blog"/><published>2022-04-23T23:20:09+00:00</published><updated>2022-04-23T23:20:09+00:00</updated><id>https://map1eum.github.io/blog/2022/displaying-external-posts-on-your-al-folio-blog</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://map1eum.github.io/blog/2022/displaying-external-posts-on-your-al-folio-blog/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author></entry></feed>